<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-13T20:02:19+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">No Time Like the Present</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/08/episode-6.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No Time Like the Present" /><published>2020-04-08T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-08T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/08/episode-6</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/08/episode-6.html">&lt;p&gt;Following the death of Goku, Bulma wonders how Raditz was able to track him down. Piccolo tells her that it was because of the sensor attached to Raditz’ face. Bulma recovers the machine and fixes it up with plans to use it to find Tien Shinhan and Yamcha. As they prepare to head back to Kame House, Piccolo regenerates his arm then tells Bulma, Krillin and Master Roshi that he wishes to take Gohan for special training. Krillin initially refuses but Piccolo explains his hidden power and it’s usefulness in the battle to come with the arriving Saiyans. He then takes the unconscious Gohan away with him, with the others being unable to do anything about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kami, having preserved Goku’s body for resurrection, escorts the late hero into the presence of the gigantic King Yemma, the judge of Heaven and Hell. He chooses to train with the great King Kai, a being whose position is above even that of King Yemma, before being resurrected by the Dragon Balls. King Yemma reveals that thousands of years ago, he too trained under this Kai, who is truly a powerful man. After receiving the King’s permission, Goku is escorted to the head of Snake Way, the route between King Yemma’s palace and King Kai’s realm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On their way back to Kame House, Krillin wonders how Chi-Chi will take the news that had happened and who should be the one to tell her, Master Roshi and Bulma urge Krillin to do so being Goku’s best friend. At Goku’s house, Chi-Chi tries phoning Kame House concerned as to why Goku and Gohan have not returned home yet but nobody answers. At the entrance to Snake Way, Goku is amazed at how long the road must be with the Guide informing him that is one million kilometers long. The Guide warns Goku not to fall off of the path because there is no way for him to return if he does. Before Goku leaves he asks the Guide of he can ask Fortuneteller Baba to tell his friends not to revive him for one year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arriving in an uninhabited area, Piccolo awakens Gohan and informs him of his father’s death. Determining the extent of Gohan’s dormant power by hurling him at a mountain which he promptly destroys, Piccolo tells him that he will draw this power out and train him, whether Gohan likes it or not. Gohan asks Piccolo why his father can’t train him when he comes back to life but Piccolo tells him that he’s too soft and they are short on time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>by Joost van Heijningen</name></author><summary type="html">Following the death of Goku, Bulma wonders how Raditz was able to track him down. Piccolo tells her that it was because of the sensor attached to Raditz’ face. Bulma recovers the machine and fixes it up with plans to use it to find Tien Shinhan and Yamcha. As they prepare to head back to Kame House, Piccolo regenerates his arm then tells Bulma, Krillin and Master Roshi that he wishes to take Gohan for special training. Krillin initially refuses but Piccolo explains his hidden power and it’s usefulness in the battle to come with the arriving Saiyans. He then takes the unconscious Gohan away with him, with the others being unable to do anything about it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gohan’s Rage</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/07/episode-5.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gohan's Rage" /><published>2020-04-07T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/07/episode-5</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/07/episode-5.html">&lt;p&gt;Gohan bursts through Raditz’s Space Pod, shocking Piccolo and Raditz. Goku tells Gohan to run away, but Gohan is too deeply enraged to make sense of anything. Raditz, reading Gohan’s Power Level to be well above his own, begins to panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, Gohan charges at Raditz and hits him in the middle of his chest, leaving him wounded. Gohan runs to his father’s side as Raditz staggers to his feet. Goku pleads with Gohan to run, but now he is too scared to run. Raditz reads Gohan’s power again: it has substantially dropped to one. Raditz knocks Gohan unconscious, which sends him a few feet away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raditz approaches Gohan and begins to gather energy to kill him. Raditz reveals that Gohan was the first person to wound him this severely. As Raditz raises his arm for the final blow, Goku puts him in a Full-Nelson, preventing the attack. He tells Piccolo to try the Special Beam Cannon again, even if it means his own death. Piccolo, without hesitation, begins to gather energy for another Special Beam Cannon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raditz pleads with his brother to reconsider what he is doing, but Goku only holds on tighter. Piccolo finally gathers enough energy for the technique, and fires it at Raditz. The beam goes directly through both Saiyan brothers. The two fall to the ground fatally wounded. Piccolo approaches Raditz, who is lamenting that Goku foolishly sacrificed his life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Piccolo tells Raditz about the Dragon Balls and that they can grant any wish, which includes bringing the dead back to life, but Raditz secretly relays the message to his two partners in deep space. Raditz triumphantly tells them that these two are far stronger than him, and that they will very likely come to Earth to use the Dragon Balls to wish him back in one year. Raditz laughs maniacally, and an irate Piccolo finishes Raditz off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back at Goku’s House, Chi-Chi wonders what’s taking Goku and Gohan so long to return home and that he must have lost track of time. She hopes the delay won’t affect Gohan’s studies but then realises that it’s good for him to have some fun from time to time as well. The Ox-King then shows up bearing gifts asking where Gohan is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In deep space, Raditz’s partners, Vegeta and Nappa, pick up Raditz’s signal and learn of the Dragon Balls. Meanwhile, Bulma, Master Roshi, and Krillin arrive just in time to bid Goku farewell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in deep space Nappa mentions using the Dragon Balls to wish Raditz back to life but Vegeta tells him that Raditz was a weakling and it would be a waste of a wish. Vegeta decides to wish for eternal life, so they get into their Space Pods and head for Earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goku’s body begins to vanish, which Piccolo states was Kami’s doing, while everyone is left to mourn his death and prepare for the approaching threat.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>by Joost van Heijningen</name></author><summary type="html">Gohan bursts through Raditz’s Space Pod, shocking Piccolo and Raditz. Goku tells Gohan to run away, but Gohan is too deeply enraged to make sense of anything. Raditz, reading Gohan’s Power Level to be well above his own, begins to panic.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Piccolo’s Plan</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/06/episode-4.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Piccolo's Plan" /><published>2020-04-06T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-06T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/06/episode-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/06/episode-4.html">&lt;p&gt;As Goku and Piccolo charge towards Raditz to attack, he kicks out backwards and sends them rolling away. He then fires a Double Sunday that destroys Piccolo’s left arm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On their way to the Spinach Wastes, Bulma, Krillin and Master Roshi discuss Goku’s team up with Piccolo. Master Roshi expresses that teaming up with Goku is the best chance he has of defeating Raditz but Krillin is concerned over Piccolo’s evil intentions but Master Roshi says that if those two can not defeat Raditz then there is no one else left on Earth who can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Piccolo, now with only one arm, reveals that he has a secret ace up his sleeve, but will need some time before he can charge up this new attack. Thus, Goku is given the job to stall Raditz for five minutes. Goku and Raditz begin their fight, but once again Goku is unable to keep up with Raditz. He is sent crashing to the ground, and even after unleashing a Kamehameha, Goku is unable to do any kind of damage to Raditz. Raditz then blasts Goku out of the sky with Saturday Crush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the time is enough and Piccolo fires his most powerful attack, which he had originally designed to use against Goku: the Special Beam Cannon. The Cannon almost hits Raditz dead-on. However, Raditz is able to dodge it, which completely horrifies Piccolo. The attack did nothing but injure Raditz’s shoulder and damage his armor. Raditz was about to use Begone! on Piccolo, but then he stopped &amp;amp; sounded like he was in pain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon turning around, Raditz saw that Goku had grabbed his tail to weaken him. Goku squeezed it, paralyzing Raditz, and told Piccolo to use the Special Beam Cannon again. Piccolo agreed, but said that he only had enough energy to use it one more time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raditz begged for mercy, and pleaded to Goku by claiming that if he lets him go, then he’ll leave the Earth never return. Piccolo tried to warn Goku saying that it was a trick, but Goku’s mercy got the best of him. Piccolo turned out to be correct, as Raditz then elbowed Goku to the ground &amp;amp; pinned him down with his foot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raditz mocked Goku for being so easily deceived. Goku called the trick dirty, but Raditz replies with that he’s a first-class warrior and he’ll do whatever it takes to win, even deceiving his own brother. He then dared Piccolo to use the Special Beam Cannon again, but Piccolo couldn’t because he’d just dodge it again. Raditz then continues to torture Goku by crushing his ribs under his foot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back at Goku’s House, Chi-Chi prepares dinner ready for Goku and Gohan’s arrival home. She spots Gohan’s test paper and seeing his perfect score says that she ought to push him into the sciences so he could become an astronaut and travel into space some day. She then wonders when the two will hurry up and come back home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raditz continues to harm Goku as Gohan hears his screams from inside the Space Pod. Raditz suddenly picks up a large power level but is unaware of where it’s coming from. Suddenly an angered Gohan smashes through the Space Pod.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>by Joost van Heijningen</name></author><summary type="html">As Goku and Piccolo charge towards Raditz to attack, he kicks out backwards and sends them rolling away. He then fires a Double Sunday that destroys Piccolo’s left arm.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unlikely Alliance</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/05/episode-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unlikely Alliance" /><published>2020-04-05T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-05T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/05/episode-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/05/episode-3.html">&lt;p&gt;In the previous episode, we see that Raditz effortlessly defeats his younger brother Goku and kidnaps Gohan. He asks Goku to kill one hundred Earthlings and put them on the beach, if he wanted to ever see his son again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unwilling to complete the task, Goku sat there and pondered on how get his son back when his archrival, Piccolo, shows up. The others are shocked to see him and immediately take up fighting stances. Piccolo assures them that he means no harm, and offers Goku a hand in defeating Raditz. However, he states clearly that he is not doing it to save Gohan, but rather just wants to make sure Raditz does not conquer the Earth, as he wants to do it himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the others do not trust Piccolo, Goku accepts the offer. Taking Bulma’s Dragon Radar to locate the Four-Star Dragon Ball, that was on top of Gohan’s hat. Earth’s two strongest fighters then depart from Kame House to eliminate the threat and rescue Gohan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Gohan keeps annoying Raditz by crying out. Getting annoyed each second, Raditz locks Gohan in his Space Pod. This distresses Gohan further, and, for the first time, he starts demonstrating his unlimited dormant potential, as his power level skyrockets. Raditz picks it up with his scouter, but unable to believe that a child could possess such power, he dismisses it thinking that the Scouter malfunctioned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was until Goku and Piccolo arrive on the spot. Since the Scouter predicted their arrival, Raditz becomes shocked at realizing that his Scouter is not malfunctioning and that Gohan really does have a power level of 710.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goku declines the offer of life as a Saiyan and demands that Raditz give back his son. Raditz decides to give Goku one last look at Gohan before he dies. Seconds later, the powerful warriors begin to do battle. The battle is intense, but even with their combined strength, Goku and Piccolo are caught off guard by the evil Saiyan. Raditz then reveals to Goku and Piccolo that the two remaining Saiyan Warriors have an even higher power than himself much to their dismay.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>by Joost van Heijningen</name></author><summary type="html">In the previous episode, we see that Raditz effortlessly defeats his younger brother Goku and kidnaps Gohan. He asks Goku to kill one hundred Earthlings and put them on the beach, if he wanted to ever see his son again.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Reunions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/04/episode-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reunions" /><published>2020-04-04T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-04T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/04/episode-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/04/episode-2.html">&lt;p&gt;After being away for five years, Bulma is invited to Kame House, where Master Roshi and Krillin have been living and Krillin asks Bulma where Yamcha is and Bulma tells Krillin and Master Roshi that she broke up with Yamcha for good and is done with him, because he didn’t show up. Goku arrives shortly, and introduces his son, Gohan, to everyone. Master Roshi points out that Goku named him after his Grandpa Gohan. Bulma is impressed with how proper Gohan’s speech is, in light of who his parents are. Goku tells her how Chi-Chi is quite strict about the education Gohan receives, and how she does not let him train Gohan, much to everybody’s surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone then realizes that Gohan has a tail, and collectively worries, but after a delicately-worded question to Goku, they are relieved to hear that his family goes to bed early, not giving Gohan a chance to ever see a full moon. Master Roshi is surprised at how Goku still has a lot of strength, especially considering his having settled down with a wife and a child. Bulma also sees that there is a four-star Dragon Ball on his hat and it reminds her about her quest of finding the Dragon Balls with Goku. Krillin asks Goku what he should wish for if he collects all seven Dragon Balls while throwing some stones at the ocean and Goku says that he doesn’t know and throws a stone at the ocean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before they go inside, however, Goku senses a strong presence headed their way. They think it’s Piccolo from the 23rd World Martial Arts Tournament five years ago, but it’s not Piccolo. The alien soon appears. Krillin, unaware of the strength the alien possesses, attempts to show him off the island. Raditz knocks Krillin through the side of Kame House with his tail. Raditz identifies Goku as Kakarot and berates him for not completing his “mission” for years. Further complicating matters, Raditz also claims that Goku is a Saiyan warrior, and that he and Goku are, in fact, brothers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goku and Krillin understandably think that Raditz is insane, but Master Roshi reveals that there may be some truth to the evil Saiyan’s words.
Master Roshi reveals that Goku’s adopted grandfather, Gohan found a strange space capsule in the woods, containing a baby Goku. He explains that, as a baby, Goku was violent and ill-tempered. Nevertheless, an accident caused him to fall and hit his head, causing a case of amnesia in which Goku forgot about his original Saiyan programming which, in turn, changed Goku into the happy, amicable child that everyone came to know and love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This new revelation shocks Goku, who refuses to believe its validity. Raditz then goes on to state that Goku’s original purpose was to destroy all life on Earth, which he should have done in a matter of years after his arrival. Raditz also reveals that the Saiyans’ original home planet, Planet Vegeta was destroyed by an asteroid sometime after Goku’s departure to Earth and that there are only four Saiyans left, including himself and Goku.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, Raditz mentions that he needs his brother’s help in destroying all life on a distant planet. Goku refuses, which prompts Raditz to notice Gohan, who still retains his Saiyan tail, which leads Raditz to threaten the fate of the child. Goku tries to stop him, but is dealt a powerful knee strike to the stomach, which sends him plummeting to the ground. Raditz then kidnaps Gohan, and tells Goku to kill one hundred Earthlings, if he ever wishes to see his son again.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>by Joost van Heijningen</name></author><summary type="html">After being away for five years, Bulma is invited to Kame House, where Master Roshi and Krillin have been living and Krillin asks Bulma where Yamcha is and Bulma tells Krillin and Master Roshi that she broke up with Yamcha for good and is done with him, because he didn’t show up. Goku arrives shortly, and introduces his son, Gohan, to everyone. Master Roshi points out that Goku named him after his Grandpa Gohan. Bulma is impressed with how proper Gohan’s speech is, in light of who his parents are. Goku tells her how Chi-Chi is quite strict about the education Gohan receives, and how she does not let him train Gohan, much to everybody’s surprise.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A new threat</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/03/episode-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A new threat" /><published>2020-04-03T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-04-03T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/03/episode-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/03/episode-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Five years have passed since the events of Dragon Ball, and the world is enjoying a reign of peace. Little do the people of Earth know, a new threat is coming to Earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The episode begins with Chi-Chi calling for her son, Gohan. The scene goes to Goku, hopping through the forest behind his house looking for some firewood. After finding and knocking down one of the largest trees in the forest with one punch, he picks it up and heads for home. When he gets there, Chi-Chi asks him to go out into the woods and look for Gohan, so they can go to Kame House. Goku agrees, and Chi-Chi tells him to take the Flying Nimbus so they are not late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, a Farmer is working in a field, putting a stack of hay into his truck, when he hears a strange noise. He looks up to see a meteorite fall and crash in the fields. The farmer asks himself, “why me?” and gets in his truck to check it out. The farmer takes his pea-shooter with him for protection. He gets to the crater and sees it was not a meteorite at all, but a steel ball of some sort. The ship opens up and a man steps out of it and realizes that everything on Earth is not destroyed. The man floats out of the crater, the farmer loads his gun and tells the alien (nervously) that he is on his property. The alien presses the button on his scouter and reads his Power Level, which is 5. The farmer shoots his gun, but the mysterious invader catches the bullet in his hand and flicks it back at him, seemingly killing the farmer. His scouter then picks up a high Power Level and he takes off after it, calling “Prepare yourself, Kakarot!”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scene then goes to little Gohan in the woods, lost and scared. He calls out for his daddy, then starts to cry and runs through the woods. He stops at the giant stump, where Goku knocked down the tree, and sits down, looking up. He sees a beautiful blue and black butterfly land on the tree stump, and as he gets up, the butterfly flies away. Gohan chases after it and it lands on high up on a tree. Gohan tries to climb up to reach it but miserably fails. He looks around and when he comes back, the butterfly flies away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gohan walks out of the woods and hears a noise in the bushes, and thinking it is the butterfly, walks up to it. Instead of a butterfly, it is a Sabertooth Cat. Gohan tries to run but trips on the ground. Gohan decides the best way is to play dead, so he lays on the ground. The tiger becomes confused and licks Gohan’s face. It tastes him, then takes his red hat (that has a Dragon Ball on it) and runs away with it. Gohan gets up, and realizing that his hat is gone, starts crying, exclaiming his dad gave him that hat. He gets up and runs into the woods to chase the tiger. The tiger turns around, and seeing the crying boy chasing him, runs as fast as he can. The tiger tries to lose Gohan every way he can, going through bushes, around trees, and over large rocks and he still does not lose him. The tiger finally takes a sharp turn and Gohan goes straight through bushes, and over a cliff. Gohan falls quickly, and as he falls, he faints. When Gohan wakes up, he is hanging from his tail upside down from a tree inches away from the ground and not hurt at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a quick scene, Goku is by the stump Gohan was sitting on earlier, calling for him. It then goes back to Gohan trying to get across a river using stepping stones. He barely gets on one and calls for his mommy and daddy again. He gets across the river and is walking along the rocks when he sees a blue bird roosting on a log hanging over the river. He says “Hello” to the bird and gets on the log to talk to it. He introduces himself to it and it flies away, so he tries to reach for it, but the log unhinges itself from the rock and Gohan goes into the river with the log. When he tries to grab onto it, the log spins, sending him further down the river, and Gohan calls for his parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Goku is looking around and he sees the Sabertooth Cat with a hat on. He recognizes it as Gohan’s hat, so Goku asks the tiger if he has seen him. The tiger growls at Goku and Goku asks again, but more angrily, scaring the tiger. The hat drops off its head and it runs into the woods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to Gohan, he is going down the river on the log when it hits a rock. Gohan lets go of the log and flails around trying to grab the log. He grabs it and calls for his mom and dad repeatedly. Above, Goku is looking for Gohan using the Flying Nimbus and sees his son flailing on the log in the river. Goku calls his name and Gohan calms down once he sees his father above him. He accidentally lets go of the log and grabs the end of it when it turns around. He flies down, and once he is about to reach Gohan, he must fly up because of a small cave the river goes into. Goku flies up as fast as the Nimbus can go to get over the very large plateau. The cave ends at a waterfall, and before Goku can get to Gohan, Gohan goes over. Goku, thinking his son went over the edge, is about to jump over when he hears him crying above. He looks up to see Gohan crying on top of a tree branch hanging over the cliff, above the waterfall. Goku flies up with the Nimbus and Gohan jumps and hugs his dad, thanking his dad for saving him. Goku asks how he got up there. Gohan says that he lost his hat, and Goku puts it on, telling him to go get cleaned up so they can go to Master Roshi’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over a city, the mysterious alien is flying in disgust. The scene goes to the evil Piccolo in a wasteland when he feels a huge power coming toward him. The alien lands and says he thought that Piccolo was this ‘Kakarot’. He reads Piccolo’s Power Level (which is 322) and says he would be a fool to attack him. Piccolo says he has no intention of starting a fight, but the alien says he does. Piccolo gets mad and fires an Explosive Demon Wave at him, thinking he has destroyed him. However, when the dust clears, the mysterious alien is not even hurt at all. He is about to attack Piccolo with an energy attack, when his scouter goes off. He flies off, saying it is Kakarot for sure. Piccolo gets down and breathes, saying how he hit him full force and he did not even flinch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mysterious Saiyan is flying towards the Power Level on his scouter and talks about how he still remembers the day they sent Kakarot to Earth.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>by Joost van Heijningen</name></author><summary type="html">Five years have passed since the events of Dragon Ball, and the world is enjoying a reign of peace. Little do the people of Earth know, a new threat is coming to Earth.</summary></entry></feed>